(dog barking)
♪ Nobody gets me like you ♪
♪ How am I supposed to let you go ♪
♪ Only like myself when I'm with you ♪
♪ Nobody gets me, you do ♪
♪ You do ♪
(engine rumbling)
- "I wish it didn't have to
be this way, I really do."
"Sometimes in life, we have
to protect our own heart."
"Even if it means ripping
it out of our chest."
"Au revoir mon amour."
(gunshots firing)
(dog barking in distance)
♪ I'm still a fan, even
though I was salty ♪
♪ Hate to see you with some
other broad, now you happy ♪
♪ Hate to see you happy, if
I'm not the one driving ♪
♪ I'm so mature, I'm so mature ♪
♪ I'm so mature ♪
♪ I got me a therapist to
tell me there's other men ♪
♪ I don't want none, I just want you ♪
♪ If I can't have you, no one should ♪
♪ I might ♪
♪ I might kill my ex, not the best idea ♪
♪ His new girlfriend's
next, how'd I get here ♪
♪ I might kill my ex, I
still love him though ♪
♪ Rather be in jail than alone ♪
♪ I get the sense that it's a lost cause ♪
♪ I get the sense that you
might really love her ♪
♪ This text gon' be evidence,
this text is evidence ♪
♪ I try to ration with you ♪
♪ No morals or crimes
of passion, but damn ♪
♪ You was out of reach ♪
♪ You was at the farmer's market ♪
♪ With your perfect peach ♪
♪ Now I'm in the basement ♪
♪ Planning home invasion ♪
♪ Now you laying face-down ♪
♪ Got me singing over a beat ♪
♪ I'm so mature, I'm so mature ♪
♪ I'm so mature ♪
♪ I got me a therapist to
tell me there's other men ♪
♪ I don't want none, I just want you ♪
♪ If I can't have you, no one will ♪
♪ I might kill my ex, not the best idea ♪
♪ His new girlfriend's
next, how'd I get here ♪
♪ I might kill my ex, I
still love him though ♪
♪ Rather be in jail than alone ♪
♪ I did it all for love ♪
♪ I did it all on no drugs ♪
♪ I did all of this sober ♪
♪ I did it all for us, oh ♪
♪ I did it all for love ♪
♪ I did it all of this on no drugs ♪
♪ I did all of this sober ♪
♪ Don't you know I did it all for us ♪
♪ Uh, I just killed my
ex, not the best idea ♪
♪ Killed his girlfriend
next, how'd I get here ♪
♪ I just killed my ex, I
still love him, though ♪
♪ Rather be in Hell than alone ♪
♪ You push me past my own capacity, boy ♪
♪ Permission to crash,
collecting damages, boy ♪
♪ No reaching and grabbing
for more clarity now ♪
♪ Seek and destroy,
all missiles deployed ♪
♪ Do it to you, do it to you ♪
♪ I had to do it you ♪
♪ Do it you, oh ♪
♪ Don't make me do it to you ♪
♪ Do it to you, do it to you ♪
♪ I hate to do it to you ♪
♪ Do what I gotta do ♪